https://www.tabbysplace.org/privacy-policy/

Our History
What Is Tabby’s Place?
Tabby's Place > Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Tabby’s Place collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this Web site (each, a “User”).
Note: Tabby’s Place will not sell, rent or disclose your personally identifiable information to any third parties.
How We Collect Information
Users will not be implicitly added to any mailing lists. Users subscribe to mailing lists by explicitly providing us with an email address on our web site. The User has the right to opt-in or opt-out at any time.
The Information We Collect
We may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. We may also collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views for the pages of the Web site or the domains from which Users originate. We may use “cookies” to track how Users use our Web site. (A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Users’ PC and use to identify the User should they revisit the Web site.) While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Web site.
How We Use Information
Tabby’s Place may use personally identifiable information collected through our Web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by us and otherwise to enhance Users’ experience with Tabby’s Place. We may also use information collected through our Web site for research regarding the effectiveness of the Web site and our marketing, advertising and sales efforts.
Disclosure of Information
Tabby’s Place will not disclose information collected from Users to third parties. However, we may disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from Users.
Maintenance of Information
Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures.
Google Analytics Advertising Features
This web site has enabled Google Analytics Advertising Features that allows Google to collect data about our traffic via Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers.
We only use this information to view aggregate demographics of our users.
See this page for information on how you can opt out of the collection by Google of this data.
Questions
Users may direct questions concerning this Privacy Policy by email to info@tabbysplace.org.
About
Our History
What Is Tabby’s Place?
Search for:
Assessment
×
